const STORE = [
    {
        question: "Blood sugar is also known as?",
        answer: "Glucose",
        choices: ["Frutose","Glucose","Cellulose"],
    },
    {
        question: "Food with a high glycemic index means:",
        answer: "it contains alot of glucose.",
        choices: ["it contains alot of glucose.","there is a net amount of glucose.","there is a high amount of fat."],
    },
    {
        question: "Diabetics can eat:",
        answer: "All of the above",
        choices: ["Fish, meats, cheese, ice cream","Meat, sugar-free food, nuts","Meat, fruits, potatoes","All of the above","None of the above"],
    },
    {
        question: "You are more likely to get diabetes if:",
        answer: "your parent has it.",
        choices: ["your parent has it.","you are overweight.","you eat a lot of sugar."],
    },
    {
        question: "What's makes Type 1 different from Type 2?",
        answer: "Your body doesn't make its own insulin.",
        choices: ["It's the good one.","Your body doesn't make its own insulin.","Your body is resistant to insulin.", "You get it when your are young."],
    },
    {
        question: "Low blood sugar is also called:",
        answer: "Hypoglycemia",
        choices: ["Hypoglycemia","Hyperglycemia","Hypothyroidism", "Hypothalamus"],
    },
    {
        question: "What's one way to raise blood sugar quickly?",
        answer: "Drink some juice.",
        choices: ["Eat a steak.","Eat some nuts.","Drink some water.","Drink some juice."],
    },
    {
        question: "How many grams of carbohydrates is in a 375ml can of Coke?",
        answer: "39.8",
        choices: ["39.8","21.5","45.6","38.9"],
    },
    {
        question: "How does carbohydrates affect diabetes?",
        answer: "It raises your blood sugar level.",
        choices: ["It doesn't do anything.","It raises your blood sugar level.","It drops your blood sugar level."],
    },
    {
        question: "What does insulin do to our blood sugar?",
        answer: "It regulates it.",
        choices: ["It raises it.","It regulates it.","It gets rid of blood sugar."],
    },

]